Guide to the William A. Speck Collection of Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 30.02; (21 boxes) + 204 broadside folders
  - DRAWERS: VIEWS
    - Italy
      - Campi Flegrei (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Castel Gandolfo (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Girgenti (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Frascati (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Napoli (Box bsd, Folder ++)
      - Padova (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Pesto (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Pozzuoli (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Segeste (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Selinunte (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Taormina (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Tivoli (Box bsd, Folder +)
  - DRAWERS: ILLUSTRATIONS
    - Goethe's Works: H. Steiner - Prag. (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Dichtung und Wahrheit (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Don Juan - Bilderbogen (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Egmont (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Faust
      - Am Brunnen (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Auerbach's Keller (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - König von Thule (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Gretchens Stube (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Studierzimmer (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Strasse vor Gretchen's Tür (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Kerker (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Garten, Gartenhäuschen (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Dom (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Miscellaneous (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Carstens (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Seibertz (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Gretchen (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Nauwerck (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Stage Sets (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Bilderbogen (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Mater Dolorosa (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Moving Picture - MGM - UFA Film (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Mephistopheles (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Walpurgisnacht (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Faust (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Rembrandt (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Pecht (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Th. II (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Strasse (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Osterspaziergang (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Related Material (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Die Fischerin (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Götz von Berlichingen (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Der Gross - Cophta (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Hermann und Dorothea (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Iphigenie (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Neuestes aus Plundersweilern / Proserpina. Melodram (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Römisches Carneval / Schiller. Don Carlos (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Schiller. Wallensteins Lager (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Der Verbrecher aus Verlorener Ehre (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Wahlverwandtschaften (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Werther
      - Northcote - Knight - 1784 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Kingsbury - 1783 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Werther und Lotte (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Ramberg, Bunbury (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Xenien (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Miscellaneous engravings by various artists including Daniel Chodowiecki, Salomon Gessner, Wilhelm Friedrich Gmelin, Johann Heinrich Lips, and Johann Heinrich Meyer (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Unidentified (Box bsd, Folder +)